# **Duy Nguyen Cong (Pauli)**



I have an extensive background as a production thermal engineer in Vietnam, which respectively helped me master programming faster and become a Full Stack Developer.

I have been programming for the past 3 years and further improving my front-end and back-end development skills. I am passionate about my long-term future as a Senior Developer leading diverse development projects.

#### **Contact information**

**Phone** +358 46 681 5155

Email ncongduy@gmail.com

Linkedin <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/duy-nguyen-cong-55b850197/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/duy-nguyen-cong-55b850197/</a>

Github <a href="https://github.com/ncongduy">https://github.com/ncongduy</a>

Portfolio website <a href="https://ncongduy.github.io/myPortfolio/">https://ncongduy.github.io/myPortfolio/</a>

# **Recent projects**

# **Country information**

TypeScript, React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, React Router Dom, Material-UI

- The website is build to find information about 250 countries in the world.
- Git repo: <a href="https://github.com/ncongduy/country-information">https://github.com/ncongduy/country-information</a>
- Demo: <a href="https://country-information-app.netlify.app/">https://country-information-app.netlify.app/</a>

#### Multi-travel app

Express.js, localStorage, JavaScript, SCSS, Service Workers, Webpack, Jest

- A web-based application, which provides the users with the location, time, temperature and date based on their location.
- Git repo: https://github.com/ncongduy/travel-app-project5-udacity
- Demo: <a href="https://travel-app-project5-udacity.herokuapp.com/">https://travel-app-project5-udacity.herokuapp.com/</a>

# **Experience**

#### Full-stack developer

Integrify | Helsinki, Finland | January 2022 - Present

- Sharpening competence as a Full Stack Developer by collaborating with other developers of different seniorities on a diverse range of projects and real-life challenges.
- Focusing on front-end development with JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Redux in addition to other technologies and concepts such as accessibility and animations.
- Building back-end for web-based applications with frameworks such as Node.js and Express.js.
- Covering additional concepts such as API development and documentation, unit testing with Jest, SQL and NoSQL databases, and version control with GitHub.
- Working with DevOps practices (Bash scripting, Docker containers, and CI/CD with GitHub Actions).

#### **Product trainer**

Mitsubishi Electric Vietnam | Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam | April 2019 - August 2017

- Presented over 20 new products to the customers of Mitsubishi and, as a result, increased B2B sales.
- Provided market research and insights to the marketing and product teams.
- Provided sales training to over 50 employees in Vietnam.

#### Thermal engineer

Enerteam | Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam | January 2013 - December 2017

- Conducted energy audits for over 100 companies to reduce on average from 10% to 30% of their energy consumption and costs.
- Gathered electricity consumption and fuel information for industrial, and food companies to analyze the data using electricity meters.
- Provided solutions through calculated measures for energy saving resulting in decreased energy consumption.
- Proposed sustainable development strategies such as bio-fuel and solar panel usage for electricity consumption.

#### **Education**

#### Nano Degree Program of Front End Web Developer

Udacity | Remote, (Online) | 44470

#### **B.SC.** In Thermal Engineering

Bach Khoa University | Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam | September 2007 - June 2013

#### **Skills**

# **Highlighted skills**

JavaScript, React.js, Redux, Git, Express

# Front-end development

HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Accessibility, Boostrap, Material-UI, React, Redux, React Router Dom

# **Back-end development**

Node.js, Express.js, Rest Api

# **Database management**

MongoDB, Mongoose, PostgreSQL, Sequelize

# **Testing**

Jest

### **DevOps**

Git, Github, Bash script, Docker

# Language

**English** Fluent

Finnish Intermediate

Vietnamese Native

# **Certificate**

• React Course, Codecademy (July 2021).

- Redux Course, Codecademy (July 2021).
- HTML Course, Codecademy (April 2021).
- Command Line Course, Codecademy (February 2021).
- Git Course, Codecademy (September 2020).
- Building Interactive JavaScript Websites Course, Codecademy (August 2020).
- Suomea A2.2, Taitotalo (Jan 2022).
- Suomea A2.1, Axxell (June 2021).